A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Education, 2006-2014 (bulk 2009-2013)
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Records of the Office of the Secretary of Education, 2006-2014 (bulk 2009-2013)
The Library of Virginia
51121
15 cu. ft. (15 Boxes).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Office of the Secretary of Education, Patrick Henry Building, 1111 E. Broad Street, Richmond, Virginia, 23219. Accession 51121 transferred and accessioned on 12 January 2010.
Biographical/Historical Information
The Secretary of Education assists the Governor of Virginia in the development and implementation of the state's education policy. The secretary provides guidance to 16 colleges and universities, the Virginia Community College System, five higher education and research centers, the Department of Education, the state-supported museums, and other agencies in the Education Secretariat. All secretaries are appointed by the governor.
This collection includes material from the Secretary of Education during the administrations of Governors Robert F. McDonnell (2010-2014) and Timothy M. Kaine (2006-2010). The bulk of the material stems from the former. The Secretariats of Education directed policy for education programs that involve multiple agencies including: Department of Education, Library of Virginia, Frontier Culture Museum of Virginia, Gunston Hall, Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Science Museum of Virginia and Virginia Commission for the Arts. While Virginia's Colleges and Universities are semi-autonomous, the Secretary of Education also plays a role in directing state policy for: Virginia Community Colleges, Christopher Newport University, George Mason University, James Madison University, Longwood University, Mary Washington University, Norfolk State University, Old Dominion University, Radford University, Richard Bland College, University of Virginia, Commonwealth University, Virginia Military Institute, Virginia State University, Virginia Tech, College of William and Mary, Roanoke Higher Education Center, Southwest Virginia Higher Education Center, and State Council of Higher Education.
Some of the major education initiatives of the Governors secretariats during these years were: early childhood initiatives, K-12 Education reform, the All Students program, charter school initiatives, gubernatorial transition commissions, Race to the Top Federal Funding, and teacher quality. On March 26, 2010, for example, Governor Bob McDonnell signed Executive Order number nine establishing the Governor's Commission on Higher Education Reform, Innovation, and Investment; charging it with setting forth, "a comprehensive strategy for increased education attainment, skills development, and lifelong learning that will equip Virginians to succeed at the highest levels of global economic competition".
Governor Tim Kaine had named Dr. Thomas Morris as Secretary of Education on January 6, 2006. Prior to his appointment, Dr. Morris served as the president of Emory and Henry College for 13 1/2 years. A distinguished Constitutional scholar and political scientist, Dr. Morris' career at the University of Richmond spanned 21 years. For more on Secretary Morris, see the finding aid for the Secretary of Education, 2001-2010.
Governor Bob McDonnells tenure saw three different Secretaries of Education in office: Gerard Robinson (2010-2011), Laura Fornash (2011-2013), and Javaid Siddiqui (2013-2014).
Mr. Robinson was the president of the Black Alliance for Educational Options (BAEO), a national nonprofit organization. Prior to his position at BAEO, he served as a senior research associate for the School Choice Demonstration Project at the University of Arkansas from 2006 to 2007, and as a senior fellow at the Institute for the Transformation of Learning at Marquette University from 2004 to 2006. As a senior fellow, he assisted in reform efforts related to Milwaukee's private and public school choice programs and provided testimony before a Wisconsin legislative hearing on "Closing the Achievement Gap." Mr. Robinson sat on the board of the following organizations: the Policy Advisory Council at the National Alliance for Public Charter Schools; the Advisory Committee for the Program on Education Policy and Governance at Harvard University; and the Georgia GOAL Scholarship Program.
Laura W. Fornash was appointed Secretary of Education by Governor Bob McDonnell on August 23, 2011. She had served as Deputy Secretary of Education and as the Executive Director of the Governor's Commission on Higher Education Reform, Innovation, and Investment prior to said appointment.
Before joining the McDonnell administration, Mrs. Fornash spent 20 years with Virginia Tech in a number of different divisions including student affairs, continuing education, distance learning, and government relations. She was the school's Restructuring Project Director with the responsibility of managing Virginia Tech's implementation of the 2005 Restructuring Act that created new levels of operational autonomy for all public higher education institutions in exchange for meeting certain academic performance measures. She was Director of the Virginia Tech Richmond Center, an extended campus center, where credit and non credit programs were offered to working professionals. In 1998, as the Director of Information Technology Programs, Mrs. Fornash launched an innovative web based interdisciplinary masters degree program to help transition professionals into the information technology field as result of research conducted for the International Technology Association of America.
Mrs. Fornash received her undergraduate and masters degree from Virginia Tech. She is native of Chesterfield, Virginia and a graduate of Virginia public schools.
Javaid Siddiqi was appointed Secretary of Education by Governor Bob McDonnell on November 18, 2013.Prior to this appointment, he served as Deputy Secretary of Education focusing his efforts on teacher quality and improving educational outcomes for all students.
Before joining the McDonnell administration, Javaid Siddiqi spent 12 years with Chesterfield County Public Schools. During his time in Chesterfield, Dr. Siddiqi served as a high school teacher, assistant principal, and as principal of Robious Middle School where he led the implementation of Expeditionary Learning, school reform model.
Siddiqi received his undergraduate degree from Virginia Commonwealth University and his masters degree from Virginia State University, before receiving his doctorate in educational leadership at Virginia Commonwealth University. He is a native of Chesterfield and is a graduate of Virginia public schools.
Scope and Content
The Records of the Virginia Secretary of Education are housed in fifteen (15) boxes. The collection is arranged into six (6) series, as closest to original general order of material received by the Library of Virginia. Series have been designated for: I. Governor Timothy M. Kaine/Secretary Thomas R. Morris Papers, 2006-2010; II. Special Projects and Studies, 2010-2014; III. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2010-2014; IV. Legislative Files, 2010-2014; V. Budget and Planning, 2010-2014; VI. Decision Briefs and Supporting Documentation, 2010-2014.
These records include agendas, articles, briefings, correspondence, e-mails, grants, handouts, legislation, lists, memorandums, minutes, notes, presentations, press releases, reports, speeches, studies, surveys and files by subject matter or initiative title. These records document the work of the Secretary of Education for Governor Bob McDonnell as well as Governor Tim Kaine before him. The most significant and voluminous material documents the development and implementation of the various educational initiatives of the McDonnell Administration (Series II: Special Projects and Studies) including: Re-Entry programs, P-16, Gubernatorial administration transition, the work of the State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV) and K-12 education reform. When possible and appropriate, the files in each series are arranged alphabetically within.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Kaine/Morris Papers, 2006-2010 (bulk 2007-2009)
Series II. Special Projects and Studies, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Series III. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Series IV. Legislative Files, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Series V. Budget and Planning, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Series VI. Decision Briefs and Supporting Documentation, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)
Related Material
OFFICE OF THE GOVERNOR-TIM KAINE
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine Administration Electronic Files, Email, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
The Library of Virginia Email Project - Governor Tim Kaine Portal provides access to the Kaine email collection and includes guides to other Kaine administration records.
The Governor Tim Kaine Administration Web Archive Collection, 2006-2010
The Timothy M. Kaine Administration (2006-2010) Cabinet Weekly Reports Digital Collection
The Executive Orders Digital Collection
A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Policy Office, Records, 2002-2010 (bulk 2006-2009).
OFFICE OF THE GOVERNOR-ROBERT F. MCDONNELL
The Governor Robert F. McDonnell Administration Web Archive Collection, 2006-2010
The Constituent Correspondence of Governor Robert F. McDonnell Collection
The Correspondence and Supporting Documentation of the Executive Office of Governor Robert F. McDonnell Collection
The Records of the Executive Mansion of Governor Robert F. McDonnell Collection
The Records of Governor Robert F. McDonnell's Secretary of Transportation Collection
The Records of Governor Robert F. McDonnell's Governor Robert F. McDonnell, Executive Office-Deputy Chief of Staff Matt Conrad, Records, Collection
Contents List
- I. Governor Timothy M. Kaine/Secretary Thomas R. Morris Papers, 2006-2010 (bulk 2007-2009)., Extent: 2 cu. ft. (2 boxes).
  The series consists material and record types found in the other series of this collection, such as legislative material, agendas, agreements, briefings, correspondence, studies, budget material, handouts, memorandum, notes, presentations, and reports. These are grouped together in this series as they are material from a previous gubernatorial cabinet and Secretariat than the rest of the collection.
  Some of the notable files in this series relates to the following topics: No Child Left Behind, Tuition Assistant Grant Program (TAG), education funding, Standards of Learning (SOL), Standards of Quality (SOQ), budget cuts in state aid to public libraries, early childhood education, Start Strong Council, college financial aid, teacher salaries, Small, Women, and Minority-Owned Business Program (SWAM), P-16 Education Council, and campus security.
  - 2008-2010 Appropriation Act 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Base Adequacy Funding Guidelines 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Blue Book 2009 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board Initiatives 2007-2009 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board Initiatives 2007-2009 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Bonds 2009 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bridging Boundaries International 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Career Pathways 2009 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - College Workforce 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - College/Career Readiness 2009 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Commonwealth Scholars 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence 2007 2007 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence 2008 2008 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence 2009 2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence 2010 2010 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence 2010 2010 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2008 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2009 (1 of 6) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2009 (2 of 6) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2009 (3 of 6) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2009 (4 of 6) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2009 (5 of 6) (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2009 (6 of 6) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Early Childhood Advisory Council 2009 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Emails 2010 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Executive Orders 2009 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Governor's Conference 2009 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Grants 2008 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Gunston Hall 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Higher Education Funding 2006-2010 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - HJ 91 2009 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Invitations 2010 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - James Madison University 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - P-16 Education Council 2005-2009 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - P-16 Education Council 2005-2009 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - P-21 2009 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Public Broadcasting Board 2008-2010 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Public Broadcasting Board 2008-2010 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Public Charter Schools 2007-2009 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Radford University 2008 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Re-Entry 2009 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Rule of Law Project 2009-2010 (1 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Rule of Law Project 2009-2010 (2 of 2) (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Security Task Force 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV) 2008-2009 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Level II 2006-2009 (1 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Level II 2006-2009 (2 of 5) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Level II 2006-2009 (3 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Level II 2006-2009 (4 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV): Level II 2006-2009 (5 of 5) (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHEV) Reports 2006-2009 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (SREB) 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - State Board 2009 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Tredegar 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Virginia Association of School Superintendents (VASS) 2008-2011 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Tech 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Virginia Freedom of Information Act Advisory Council (VFOIA) 2008 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (VMFA) Budget 2008 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Virginia Military Institute (VMI) 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Virginia Preschool Initiative (VPI) Funding 2008-2010 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Weekly Reports 2008 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - William and Mary 2008 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Workforce Data 2009 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Workforce Development 2008-2009 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Plan Summary 2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Christopher Newport University (CNU) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - George Mason University (GMU) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - James Madison University (JMU) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Longwood University 2007 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - University of Mary Washington 2007 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Norfolk State University (NSU) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Old dominion University (ODU) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Radford University 2007 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Richard Morris College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - University of Virginia (UVA) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia Commonwealth University (VCU) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia Military Institute (VMI) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia Tech 2007 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia State University 2007 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Patrick Henry Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Paul D. Camp Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Piedmont Virginia Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Rappahannock Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Southside Virginia Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Southwest Virginia Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Thomas Nelson Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Tidewater Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia Community College System (VCCS) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia Highland Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia Western Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Wytheville Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Commission for the Arts 2007 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Department of Education 2007 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Frontier Culture Museum 2007 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation 2007 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Library of Virginia 2007 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Science Museum 2007 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - State Council of Higher Education 2007 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts (VMFA) 2007 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - William and Mary 2007 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Blue Ridge Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Central Virginia Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Dabneys Lancaster Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Danville Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Eastern Shore Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Germanna Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - John Tyler Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Lord Fairfax Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Mountain Empire Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - New River Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Small, Women-owned and Minority-owned Business (SWAM) - Northern Virginia Community College 2007 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- II. Special Projects and Studies, 2010-2014 (bulk 2010-2013)., Extent: 7 cu. ft. (7 boxes).
  Given the lack of significant provenance-based original order, this series contains reports, studies, briefings, and handouts related to commissions, meetings, events, and presentations related to education initiatives of the three secretaries that served in Governor McDonnell's cabinet.
  Some of the significant education related initiatives and topics include the following: Juvenile Re-Entry Programs and Initiatives, Tuition Assistant Grant Program (TAG), education funding, Standards of Learning (SOL), Standards of Quality (SOQ), charter schooling, early childhood education, Start Strong Council, college financial aid, teacher salaries, Small, Women, and Minority-Owned Business Program (SWAM), P-16 Education Council, and campus security.
  - ACT (American College Testing) 2012 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Action Clinic Summit 2011 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Adult Education and Literacy 2009 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Aerojet 2012 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Apprenticeships 2011 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Aviation and Aerospace Workforce 2011 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Boards and Commissions 2010 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 2011 Board Report 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 2011 Board Report 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 2011 Bridging Richmond 2011 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Building Excellent Schools Fellowship 2011 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Bullying 2012 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Campus Prep Conference 2010 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Capital Outlay Projects 2012 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Career College Association 2010 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Career Pathways 2010-2011 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Career Pathways 2010-2011 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Career Pathways 2012 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Career Pathways 2012 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Catholic Schools 2011 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Charter Incubator 2011 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Charter School Committee 2010-2012 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Charter School Committee 2010-2012 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Charter Schools 360 Report 2010 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Children's Science Center 2013 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Council of Independent Colleges in Virginia(CICV) Briefing 2010 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - College Access Grant 2010-2011 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - College Access Grant 2010-2011 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - College Application Week 2012 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - College Board 2011 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - College Board 2011 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - College Completion and Affordability 2012 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - College Partnership Lab 2011-2012 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - College/Career Readiness 2010 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - College Savings 2010 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Commission on Economic Development 2010 (1 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Commission on Economic Development 2010 (2 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Commission on Economic Development 2010 (3 of 3) (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Community Relations 2010 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Council on Economic Education 2011 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Council on Virginia's Future 2010 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Center of Innovative Technology (CIT) 2010 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Center of Innovative Technology (CIT) 2012 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Career and Technical Education (CTE) 2013 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - College Board 2012 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Communities in Schools 2010-2011 (1 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Communities in Schools 2010-2011 (2 of 2) (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Council on Economic Education 2010 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Department of Correctional Education 2010 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Data Integration 2012 (Box 4, Folder 3)